ALEXANDER MATHEWS

Seattle, Washington 208-818-5993 alexandermathews648@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/alexanderemathews/

SUMMARY

Web developer with a background in sales, customer service and management where organizational skills were developed. Experienced in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, React and Angular and eager contribute to the tech industry in the Seattle, Washington area.

EXPERIENCE

AGENCY PRODUCER/ACCOUNT MANAGER, STATE FARM INSURANCE AGENCY; SEATTLE, WASHINGTON – JUNE 2022 - SEPTEMBER 2024

- Solicited and processed intricate applications for new insurance policies including auto, home, life, supplemental health and business insurance to ensure policies properly issued for customers based on their coverage needs.
- Serviced existing accounts with tasks such as processing payments, replacing insured vehicles
 and handling customer inquiries, so customer's accounts were kept current while they remained
 informed of all updates and account status.
- Sent proof of insurance to various finance companies proving customers had coverage necessary to qualify for certain financial loans.

SHIFT LEAD, HEARTBEET ORGANIC SUPERFOODS CAFE; SEATTLE, WASHINGTON –
APRIL 2021 - JUNE 2022

- Made various menu items while logging each order for quality assurance which led to a more accurate count for the nightly inventory order.
- Guided employees through opening and closing shifts, making sure tasks were completed adequately, in a timely manner which led to more efficient night hours for the restaurant.
- Assembled large catering orders, ensuring timely delivery and customer satisfaction.
- Submitted nightly inventory orders to ensure the restaurant had all items needed to be successful for the next day.

SHIFT MANAGER, DOMINOS PIZZA; COEUR D' ALENE, IDAHO – AUGUST 2015 - MARCH 2021

 Guided employees in a fast-paced work environment to ensure employee and customer satisfaction along with restaurant efficiency.

EDUCATION

CAREERFOUNDRY – FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT, NOVEMBER 2023 - OCTOBER 2024